recipesecrets.net 2016-12-06

# Free Restaurant Recipes with various secret recipes tips

We at RecipeSecrets.net know that privacy is one of the most important issues for all of us on the Internet.  The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for RecipeSecrets.net.

Your email address is kept secure. We will not rent, sell, or exchange your contact information with anyone, with the exceptions of if we were ever merged with or acquired by another company or sold substantially all of our assets, or if we acquire another business entity or substantially all of its assets or we are involved in a corporate reorganization or other change of control, some or all of the personal information collected about you could be shared with this entity, and it may also be retained by us.

We will not otherwise share, sell, distribute, or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law or is necessary to protect our business, the users of our Marketing Channels, the Marketing Channels or the public.

Subscribers can unsubscribe at any time and are under no obligation to receive our communications.  RecipeSecrets.net is legally bound by the guidelines set forth in this privacy policy.

** How We Use Data**

We collect customer information to enhance or products and the service we provide to our customers.

From time to time, RecipeSecrets.net may send promotional e-mail.  By supplying us your contact information, you agree to receive these communications.  The information you submit to RecipeSecrets.net remains your property, but by submitting that information to RecipeSecrets.net you grant us the right to use that information for internal marketing purposes.

###  Unsubscribe

We provide unsubscribe instructions **within each email** we send out.  Alternatively, you can open a ticket request at **[ www.HelpForCustomers.com](http://www.helpforcustomers.com/)** indicating you wish to unsubscribe and we will process your request within 5 business days.

###  IP Addresses/Operating System/Browser Type

When you visit our web site or click on one of our links, we may automatically record your I.P. address, operating system, and browser version. We use this information to generate usage statistics and to ensure that our site and emails are accessible to the widest possible audience. We may also use I.P. addresses to track abuse of our system.

###  Third-Party Links

This site (and our emails) contain links to other sites. RecipeSecrets.net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

###  Cookies

From time-to-time, we may use cookies to determine which third party offers our members utilize. We will never share this data in individual form.

###  Notification of Changes

RecipeSecrets.net reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time.

###  Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:  **[ www.HelpForCustomers.com](http://www.helpforcustomers.com/)**

### ** Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this site, you agree to the RecipeSecrets.net Terms and Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of the terms and policy at any time. All changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the site. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Verity Associates, LLC sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

* * *
